froknowsphoto.com 2018-03-03

# Privacy Policy | Fro Knows Photo

FroKnowsPhoto LLC (“FRO”) has created this privacy policy to inform you about our how we treat various pieces of information you provide. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the www.FroKnowsPhoto.com website.

Links to Other Websites and Opt-out Options

Any FRO website may contain links to other websites. These third-party websites have their own privacy policies and user agreements. If you have issues with these privacy policies or user agreements, you should contact the third party site directly. FRO is not responsible for the privacy practices, security practices or the content of such websites.

If you wish to opt-out of receiving any FroKnowsPhoto-related content, you need to do so through the third-party website through which you subscribed and from which you receive such content as described below.

Security

The security of this website and your information is of great importance to FRO. This website has commercially reasonable security measures in place. However, we do not and cannot represent or warrant that your access to the website is completely secure.

Information Collection/Anti-Spam Policy/Opt-out Choice

Your privacy and personal information are important to us.

We minimize the collection of your information to do our best to ensure your privacy. You may have elected to provide information to, receive content from or access content via a third party, including but not limited Feedburner, Facebook, Twitter, UStream, YouTube, iTunes, PayPal, Vimeo, Viddler, etc. These third-party services have their own privacy policies and user agreements. If you have issues with these privacy policies or user agreements, you should contact the third party directly. FRO is not responsible for the privacy practices, security practices or the content of such websites.

We collect limited information, including but not limited to nominations, information and photos related to the Community 100 and delivery information for shipment of purchased goods or prizes.

We are committed to providing users of this website with the choice to receive or not receive e-mails and/or other communications from FRO. We do not send unsolicited commercial e-mails and do not buy or sell information we collect. We strive to comply with the CAN-SPAM Act.

We do not offer or provide to third parties any information except items displayed on the website such as blog comments, photographs and accepted nominations. We do not consider information posted publicly and displayed on the website as private and may provide such information to third-parties.

If you have questions or concerns, please contact us [right here.](http://froknowsphoto.com/contact/)

Contacting FRO  
If you have questions or concerns about information collection, your privacy, or any aspect of this policy, please contact us at Fro@FroKnowsPhoto.com or phone number below. We will attempt to reply within a reasonable time period to each inquiry we receive, but we cannot guarantee any timely response.

Changes to the Privacy Policy  
FRO may change this privacy policy from time to time in its sole and absolute discretion. Please check this website regularly for changes. Substantive revisions to this privacy policy shall apply only prospectively.
